socialbluebook.com 2018-11-20

# Privacy Policy - Social Bluebook

## Our Commitment to Privacy

Social Bluebook (“SBB”, “we”, “our” or “us”) is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes the types of personal information we collect through our website at www.socialbluebook.com (the “Website”), how we use that information, who we share it with, and the choices you can make about our collection, use and disclosure of that information. This Privacy Policy only applies to information we collect on the Website. It does not apply to information collected by SBB offline or through any other means or to information collected by any third party, including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website.  By using Social Bluebook, you are also agreeing to be bound by the Google Privacy Policy ([http://www.google.com/policies/privacy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy)).

## Acceptance

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. The use of this Website constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, you may not use the Website.

## Changes

Without prior notice, SBB reserves the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. Updates to this policy will be posted to our Website and we will revise the effective date above. Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check this Privacy Policy periodically for updates.

## Collection of Information

In order to access the services we offer through the Website, you must first complete a registration form. During registration, you will be required to provide us with your contact information, such as your name and e-mail address. You will also be required to choose a user name and password. You may provide us with your login credentials for a variety of social media networks and other websites. To safeguard the confidentiality of your user name and password, DO NOT share this information with anyone.

As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies, such as cookies or web beacons, to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns. Information we collect automatically may include usage details, browser type and language, your operating system and pages viewed.

A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer that uniquely identifies your browser to remember you and your preferences when you visit the Website. For example, our Website may set a cookie on your browser that allows you to access the Website without needing to enter a password more than once during a visit. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.

## Do Not Track

We currently do not participate in any “Do Not Track” frameworks that would allow us to respond to signals or other mechanisms from you regarding the collection of your information.

## Use of Information

Most of the information collected during the registration process will be used to provide you with information that you request from us. For example, in order to provide our services, we will use the information from social media networks and other websites that you give us access to.

We use information that we collect from you to provide the Website, information that you request, notices, security alerts and customer service. For instance, if you contact us with a question or issue, we will use your contact information to answer your question or resolve your problem. We may also use your information in any other way we may describe when you provide the information and for any purpose with your consent.

We may contact you for marketing and promotional purposes by various means, including but not limited to regular mail, e-mail or telephone. You may opt out of receiving promotional or marketing communications by contacting us as provided below or clicking the unsubscribe link in the communication. We also perform statistical analyses from the demographic information you provide so as to improve our products or to gather marketing information.

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information and we do not distribute or share IP information with any third parties.

We also gather information on your social media platforms via an API (Application Program Interface). We utilize API’s for YouTube, Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, and Google Analytics. In order to calculate your platforms valuation, we require read, management, and sometimes write access to your platforms. Social Bluebook will never post on your behalf on any of these social media platforms, and all data gathered is updated on a monthly basis. 

  * To remove Social Bluebooks access to your YouTube channel, you can delete it from the “My Values” page, or via the Google security settings page at [https://security.google.com/settings/security/permissions](https://security.google.com/settings/security/permissions). Please note that this will not remove any data from your channel itself, only from Social Bluebook.

## Sharing of Information

We will not sell your personal information to any outside parties. However, we may share your personal information with our employees, affiliates and subsidiaries and with agents and contractors of SBB who have agreed to appropriate confidentiality obligations for the purposes of assisting us to provide our services or responding to questions or comments. When an agent or contractor with whom we share your information acts solely on our behalf, SBB requires that party to follow our privacy practices. In addition, with your consent, we may share your information with third parties that provide products or services that you have requested and such third parties are not acting on our behalf in these instances. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such third parties. We do not control these third parties’ policies regarding the collection or use of your information. If you have any questions about the privacy practices of a third party, you should contact them directly.

We also reserve the right to disclose your personal information to:

  * comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request,
  * enforce our terms,
  * prevent fraudulent activity, other deceptive practices or otherwise to protect the rights, property, or safety of SBB, our customers or others, or
  * a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of SBB’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by SBB about our Website users is among the assets transferred.

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

## Links

Our Website may contain links to other sites for your convenience. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We do not control these third parties’ policies regarding the collection or use of your information. If you have any questions about the privacy practices of a third party, you should contact them directly.

## Children’s Privacy

SBB does not direct its Website to children under the age of thirteen. We require registered users of the site to be at least thirteen years of age. We do not knowingly collect any information from anyone under thirteen years of age. If we learn that a user is under thirteen years of age, we will promptly delete any personal information that the individual has provided to us. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided information to SBB through the Website, please let us know at support@socialbluebook.com.

## Your California Privacy Rights

Residents of the State of California, under California Civil Code § 1798.83, have the right to request from companies conducting business in California a list of all third parties to which the company has disclosed personal information during the preceding year for direct marketing purposes. Alternatively, the law provides that if the company has a privacy policy that gives either an Opt-out or Opt-in choice for use of your personal information by third parties (such as advertisers) for marketing purposes, the company may instead provide you with information on how to exercise your disclosure choice options. SBB qualifies for the alternative option. This Privacy Policy is our comprehensive privacy statement, and we provide you with details on how you may either Opt-out or Opt-in to the use of your personal information by third parties for direct marketing purposes. Therefore, we are not required to maintain or disclose a list of the third parties that received your personal information for marketing purposes during the preceding year. If you are a California resident and request information about how to exercise your third party disclosure choices, please send a request to support@socialbluebook.com.

## Security and Protection

SBB uses commercially reasonable security measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

## Maintenance of Information

We will retain your information for as long as is necessary to fulfill any of the purposes described in this Privacy Policy or comply with applicable legislation, regulatory requests and relevant orders from competent courts.

## International Users

Our Website is hosted in the United States. If you are accessing the site from Europe, Asia or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Website, which is governed by U.S. law and this Privacy Policy, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and therefore consent to that transfer.

## Access and Correction

You may change or review your stored account information through our Website by logging in to your account at any time. In the event you forget both your username and password, please contact our Customer Service department for assistance.

You may also contact at support@socialbluebook.com to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

## Contact Us

Should you have any questions, concerns or comments about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us at any time at support@socialbluebook.com.
